#### Contact

sarahnkidd@ymail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sarah-kidd-411965a7 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Retail
Customer Service
Leadership

# Sarah Kidd

#### Travel RN

Dallas/Fort Worth Area

## Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Customer Service, Allscripts, Meditech, Epic. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science in nursing from West Coast University. Bachelor of Arts from Texas Tech University focused in Zoology, Psychology, and English.

# Experience

Fusion Medical Staffing
Travel Registered Nurse
July 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month)
arlington

Baylor Scott & White Health Staff Registered Nurse September 2018 - June 2019 (10 months) fort worth

## Education

Texas Tech University
Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Multi/Interdisciplinary Studies · (2012 - 2014)

West Coast University
Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2015 - 2017)